

Alin Stefan Olaru

I'm an ICT Engineering Graduate with a high passion for software development planning to build a career as a software developer. I see myself as an enthusiastic person that never gives up and is always ready for a challenge. For more information regarding my experience/knowledge feel free to check the provided URLs on the bottom bar, or just contact me via a call/mail or private message.

URLs on the bottom bar, or just contact me via a call/mail or private message.

9 8700 Horsens, Denmark

in linkedin.com/in/alinstefanolaru

github.com/xShteff

60904795

alinstefanola.ru

S alin shtefan

EDUCATION

Bachelor of ICT Engineering VIA University College

08/2014 - 02/2018

Horsens, Denmark

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student Software Developer EConGrid

08/2016 - 02/2018

Fredericia, Denmark

Full time intern for the first six months and continued as a part-time developer for the next year.

Some technologies used

- ASP.NET with SignalR
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Angular 5 with TypeScript and GulpJS
- ASP.NET Core 2.0
- Apache Cordova (PhoneGap)
- Xamarin

Available Reference: Thomas Hune - CEO — tsh@econgrid.com

Community Manager

InnoGames

07/2016 - 08/2017

Remote Job (Hamburg, Germany)

Achievements/Tasks

- Recruit and supervise a team of volunteers dedicated to game support
- Maintain and expand game community
- Set up game forum and recruit forum moderators
- Establish cooperation with fan projects/sites
- Plan and execute events and contests
- Reporting to the respective Product Manager

Student LecturerVIA University College

08/2015 – 01/2016

Horsens, Denmark

Achievements/Tasks

- Help students learn the basics of software development with Java
- Prepare presentations and exercises

RELEVANT SKILLS

.NET Framework			
C#			
Java			0
JavaScript			
TypeScript		0	0
Angular		0	0
Design Patterns			
Git			
Customer Interaction			
Frontend			
Backend			0
SQL		0	0

ACHIEVEMENTS

Virtual Assistant for Airport Maintenance

This is an award given by VIA University College for our final thesis. The following basis was given: "For the courage to take on a project of very high technological complexity, and for applying the complex technology with a constant eye to common sense and practical use. And, in the end, making it all work".

LANGUAGES

English				
Romanian				
Danish	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	0	0

INTERESTS

Software Development

Web Development

AR/VR Applications

Mobile (Android) Applications